This project is a part of Azure
Machine Learning Engineer
Nanodegree at Udacity.
The dataset I used is the heart
failure dataset from Kaggle.
It contains 12 features and the
death_event target column
To run the notebooks, I used
a compute instance with
STANDARD_DS12_V2 size
and a STANDARD_D2_V2 compute
cluster for the experiments.
Then, I went through the automl
notebook to find the best model
for our problem
For the autumn config, I chose
15 minutes for experiment timeout,
40 iterations with a maximum of 4
concurrent iterations
I chose accuracy to be the primary
metric, and used a 3 fold cross
validation
Then, I submitted the experiment,
and waited for it to complete
Here are some of the trained models
Our best model is a VotingEnsemble
We can see the run in Azure ML
Studio
We can see the best model and
the highest accuracy which is
0.85953
We can look at other metrics
in the metrics tab.
For the second task, I went
through the hyperparameter
tuning notebook to train a model
using HyperDrive
I created an early termination
policy using Banditpolicy
I used Random Sampling to optimize
max_tier and C
I used an SKLearn estimator
using train.py
In train.py I create a tabular
dataset from the data in my repo
and train a Logistic Regression
model
I run the experiment
In Azure Studio, I can see the
best run which has an accuracy
of 0.788888
In the notebook, I retrieve
the best model and its best
metrics
and then, I save it.
I will deploy the autumn model
since it has the highest accuracy
First, I save the model
I define the environment,
download the scoring file and
define an Inference Config
I deploy the model using ACI
enabling authentication and
app insights
We can find the endpoint in
Azure ML Studio
We can see the application insights
We can consume the endpoint by
sending requests using sample
data from the dataframe, we can
then get predictions from
the trained model
At the end, we should delete the
web service and the compute target.